[ Telephone Ringing ] [ Heartbeat ]
[ Woman Screaming ]
[ Blade Slices ]
[ Ringing ]
- Hello ? - [ Male Voice ] Hello .
- Yes ? - Who is this ?
- Who you trying to reach ? - What number is this ?
- What number are you trying to reach ? - I don 't know .
- Well , I think you have the wrong number . - Do I ?
It happens . Take it easy .
[ Hangs Up ]
[ Telephone Ringing ]
[ Rings ]
[ Groans ] Hello ?
I 'm sorry . I guess I dialed the wrong number .
- So why 'd you dial it again ? - To apologize .
- You 're forgiven . Bye now . - Wait , wait ! Don 't hang up .
- What ? - I wanna talk to you for a second .
They 've got 900 numbers for that . See ya .
[ Hangs Up ]
[ Scoffs ]
[ Crickets Chirping ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Telephone Rings ]
[ Groans ]
[ Beeps ]
- Hello ? - Why don 't you want to talk to me ?
- Who is this ? - You tell me your name , I 'll tell you mine .
[ Chuckles ] I don 't think so .
[ Rattling ]
- What 's that noise ? - Popcorn .
- You 're making popcorn ? - Uh-huh .
I only eat popcorn at the movies .
- Well , I 'm getting ready to watch a video . - Really ? What ?
Oh , just some scary movie .
- You like scary movies ? - Uh-huh .
- What 's your favorite scary movie ? - Uh , I don 't know .
You have to have a favorite . What comes to mind ?
Um , Halloween .
You know , the one with the guy in the white mask ...
who walks around and stalks babysitters ?
- [ Man ] Yeah . - What 's yours ?
Guess .
Um , Nightmare on Elm Street .
Is that the one where the guy had knives for fingers ?
- Yeah , Freddy Krueger . - Freddy , that 's right .
I liked that movie . It was scary .
Well , the first one was , but the rest sucked .
So , you got a boyfriend ?
[ Chuckles ] Why ? You wanna ask me out on a date ?
- Maybe . Do you have a boyfriend ? - Mmm , no .
- You never told me your name . - Why do you want to know my name ?
' Cause I want to know who I 'm looking at .
What did you say ?
[ Dog Barking ] I want to know who I 'm talking to .
- That 's not what you said . - What do you think I said ?
[ Switch Clicks ]
What ?
Hello ?
Look , I gotta go .
Wait ! I thought we were gonna go out .
Uh , no . I don 't think so .
Don 't hang up on me ! [ Beeps ]
[ Popping ]
[ Rings ]
Shit . [ Beeps ]
- Yes ? - I told you not to hang up on me .
- What do you want ? - To talk .
Well , dial someone else , okay ?
[ Beeps ]
[ Popping Continues ]
[ Rings ]
[ Beeps ] Listen , asshole !
No , you listen , you little bitch !
You hang up on me again , I 'll gut you like a fish , understand ?
[ Chuckles ] Yeah .
Is this some kind of joke ?
More of a game , really .
Can you handle that ,
blondie ?
- Can you see me ? - [ Breathing Heavily ]
Listen , I am two seconds away from calling the police .
They 'd never make it in time . We 're out in the middle of nowhere .
- What do you want ? - To see what your insides look like .
[ Sobs ]
[ Doorbell Ringing ] [ Screams ]
Who 's there ? Who 's there ?
I 'm calling the police .
[ Rings ] [ Screams ]
[ Beeps ] You should never say , " Who 's there ? "
Don 't you watch scary movies ? It 's a death wish .
You might as well just come out here to investigate a strange noise or something .
Look , you 've had your fun now ,
so I think you better just leave or else .
Or else what ?
Or else my boyfriend 'll be here any second , and he 'll be pissed when he finds out .
I thought you didn 't have a boyfriend .
I lied ! I do have a boyfriend , and he 'll be here any second , so your ass better be gone .
- Sure . - I swear .
He 's big and he plays football and he 'll kick the shit out of you !
I 'm getting scared . I 'm shaking in my boots .
So you better just leave .
His name wouldn 't be ... Steve , would it ?
How do you know his name ?
Turn on the patio lights ... again .
Oh , God ! [ Lock Clicks ]
- I wouldn 't do that if I were you . - Where are you ? Where are you ?
Guess .
Please don 't hurt him . [ Muffled Shouting ]
That all depends on you .
Why are you doing this ?
- I wanna play a game . - No .
- Then he dies right now ! - No ! No !
Which is it ? Which is it ?
Wha — What kind of game ?
Turn off the light . You 'll see what kind of game .
Just do it !
[ Mouthing Words ]
[ Muffled ] Casey ! No ! No !
No ! Casey !
Here 's how we play .
I ask a question . If you get it right , Steve lives .
- Please don 't do this . - Come on . It 'll be fun .
- Please . - It 's an easy category .
- Please . - Movie trivia .
- I 'll even give you a warm-up question . - Don 't do this . I can 't .
- Name the killer in Halloween . - No .
Come on ! It 's your favorite scary movie , remember ?
He had a white mask , he stalked the babysitters .
I don 't know .
- Come on . Yes , you do . - No , please .
- What 's his name ? - I can 't think .
Steve 's counting on you .
Michael . Michael , Michael —
Yes ! Very good .
- Now for the real question . - No !
But you 're doing so well . We can 't stop now .
- Please stop ! Leave us alone ! - Then answer the question . Same category .
[ Sniffles ] Oh , please stop .
Name the killer in Friday the 13th .
Jason ! Jason ! Jason !
I 'm sorry . That 's the wrong answer .
No , it 's not ! No , it 's not . It was Jason .
Afraid not . No way .
Listen , it was Jason . I saw that movie 20 goddamn times !
Then you should know Jason 's mother , Mrs. Voorhees , was the original killer .
Jason didn 't show up until the sequel .
I 'm afraid that was a wrong answer .
You tricked me .
Lucky for you , there 's a bonus round .
But poor Steve . I 'm afraid he 's out !
[ Muffled Screaming ]
[ Splattering ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Cackling ]
Hey . We 're not finished yet .
Final question . Are you ready ?
[ Sobbing ] Please . Please leave me alone .
Answer the question , and I will .
What door am I at ?
What ?
There are two main doors to your house — a front door and the patio doors .
If you answer correctly , you live .
- Very simple . - [ Gasps ]
Don 't do this . I can 't . I won 't .
Your call .
[ Screams ]
[ Footsteps ]
- [ Shouts ] - [ Screams ]
[ Groans ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Glass Smashes ]
[ Muffled Whimpering , Screaming ]
- [ Yelps ] - [ Grunts ]
[ Breathing Heavily , Whimpering ]
- [ Grunts ] - [ Groans ]
[ Car Doors Open , Close ]
[ Man , Woman Chattering ]
[ Woman ] Did you water over here today ?
- It was just that water from the rain . - They look great , don 't they ?
- [ Man ] Don 't they smell strong ? - I told you . You could send it back .
[ Continues ]
[ Weakly ] Mom !
- Jesus ! - What is it ?
[ Growls ]
Casey .
[ Smoke Alarm Beeping ]
Oh . Oh , G —
Casey ? Casey ?
Casey !
- Where is she ? - Call the police .
[ Tapping Keys ]
[ Casey Gasps , Grunts ]
Casey ! [ Casey Grunts ]
- Casey , you upstairs ? - Oh , my God . Casey , baby ?
- [ Father ] Where is she ? - [ Mother ] She 's here .
- Mama . - [ Mother ] Oh , my God , I can hear her .
- [ Weakly ] Mom . - Where is she ?
[ Gasping ]
- [ Whimpering ] - Oh , my God ! I can hear her .
- [ Gasps ] - [ Man ] Hey !
[ Rapid Beeping ]
Get in the car . Drive down to the MacKenzies ' .
- No . No , not my daughter . - Just go .
- Not my daughter . - Call the police .
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Typing ]
[ Frogs Croaking ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ] [ Typing Stops ]
[ Sighs ] [ Typing Resumes ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Glass Breaks ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Screams ]
- It 's just me . - Billy , what are you doing here ?
- Sorry . Don 't hate me . - Oh , my God .
- You sleep in that ? - Yes , I sleep in this .
My dad is in the other room . You can 't be in here .
- I 'll just stay a sec . - No . You can 't be —
[ Knocking ] [ Gasps ] Oh , no .
You gotta go . Go , go , go .
What 's going on in there ?
- Are you okay ? - Can you knock ?
- I heard screaming . - No , you didn 't .
No ?
Oh , well . I 'm hitting the sack .
My flight leaves first thing in the morning .
Now , the expo runs all weekend , so I won 't be back till Sunday .
There 's cash on the table ,
and I 'm staying at — - The Hilton .
- Out at the airport , so call if — - If I need anything . Yeah , I got it .
I could have sworn I heard screaming .
Have a good trip , okay ?
Sleep tight , sweetie .
[ Door Closes ]
[ Cartoon Voice ] Oh ! Close call .
Billy — [ Sighs ]
What are you doing here ?
It occurred to me that ...
I 've never snuck through your bedroom window .
Shh , shh , shh .
Great . And now that it 's out of your system —
I was home watching television . The , uh — The Exorcist was on .
Got me thinking of you .
It did ?
Yeah . [ Stereo On ]
It was edited for TV — all the good stuff was cut out —
♪ ♪ [ Rock Ballad ] and it got me thinking of us .
How two years ago we started off hot and heavy —
nice solid R-rating on our way to an NC-1 7 .
♪ ♪ [ Man Singing ] And how things have changed and ...
lately we 're just sort of edited for television .
Oh . So you thought you would climb in my window ...
and we 'd have a little raw footage ?
[ Laughs ] No . No , I wouldn 't dream of breaking your underwear rule .
I just — I thought maybe we could do a little on-top-of-the-clothes stuff .
Okay .
Yeah ?
Yeah .
♪ We 'll be able to fly ♪
♪ Baby , I 'm your man ♪
♪ La , la , la , la , la ♪
[ Chuckles ] Hey .
Okay . Okay , okay . Time is up , stud-bucket .
God , you see what you do to me ?
[ Laughs ] You know what my dad will do to you ?
Yeah .
- Well , I 'm going . - Okay .
♪ Romeo andJuliet ♪
♪ Are together in eternity ♪
You know , I appreciate the romantic gesture .
♪ So , come on , baby ♪ Hey .
About the , uh , sex stuff — ♪ Take my hand ♪
I 'm not trying to rush you at all .
I was only half serious .
[ Laughs ] Okay .
♪ Baby , I 'm your man ♪
Hey , Billy .
Would you settle for a PG-1 3 relationship ?
What 's that ?
♪ La , la , la , la , la ♪
- [ Chuckles ] - [ Laughs ]
My God . You 're just a tease .
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
[ Chattering ]
There 's blood found ? All right .
[ Woman ] ... are doing drugs , that they are high in the classrooms ,
and that they are involved in the occult .
- [ Woman # 2 ] Occult ? - [ Voices Overlapping ]
[ Woman # 3 ] The small town of Woodsboro , California , was devastated last night ...
when two young teenagers were found brutally murdered .
Authorities have yet to issue a statement ,
but our sources tell us that no arrest has been made ...
and the murderer could strike again .
- Do you believe this shit ? - [ Gasps ] Tatum !
- What is going on ? - You don 't know ?
No .
Casey Becker and Steve Orth were killed last night .
What ? No way !
And we 're not just talking killed . We 're talking splatter-movie killed .
Ripped open from end to end .
Casey Becker . She sits next to me in English .
Not anymore .
It 's so sad . Her mom and dad , they found her hanging from a tree ,
her insides on the outside .
Oh , my God !
- Do they know who did it ? - Fucking clueless .
I mean , they 're interrogating the entire school — teachers , students , janitors .
- They think it 's school-related ? - They don 't know .
Dewey was saying this is the worst crime they 've seen in years ,
even worse than —
[ School Bell Rings ] Well , it 's bad .
- Here you go , Mrs. Tate . - Thank you , James .
[ Tate ] Sidney .
It would appear to be your turn .
- Who 's up next ? - Uh , Sidney Prescott .
- She was daughter of , uh — - [ Clears Throat ]
- Sidney . How you feelin ' ? - Fine .
Hi , Sidney .
Sheriff Burke , Dewey .
Uh , that 's Deputy Riley today , Sid .
- [ Burke ] How is everything ? - Good .
And your dad ? How 's he doin ' ?
We 're fine . Thanks .
We 're gonna keep this very brief , Sidney .
The police just want to ask you a few questions . You okay ?
Mm-hmm .
Sidney , were you very close to Casey Becker ?
[ Man On P. A. ] Remember , your principal loves you , and I want you to be safe .
All students are encouraged to return to their homes promptly from school grounds .
Avoid strangers . Walk in twos and threes .
[ Tatum ] What kind of questions did they ask you , Sidney ?
They asked if I knew Casey .
Yeah . They asked me that too .
- Hey , they ask if you like to hunt ? - Yeah , they did . They ask you ?
Hunt ? Why would they ask you if you like to hunt ?
' Cause their bodies were gutted .
Thank you , Randy .
They didn 't ask me if I like to hunt .
That 's ' cause there 's no way a girl could 've killed ' em .
That is so sexist . The killer could easily be female .
Basic Instinct ?
That was an ice pick . Not exactly the same thing .
Yeah , Casey and Steve were completely hollowed out .
And the fact is , it takes a man to do something like that .
Or a man 's mentality .
How do you ... gut someone ?
You take a knife ,
and you slit ' em from groin to sternum .
Hey . It 's called tact , you fuck-rag .
Hey , Stu , didn 't you used to date Casey ?
Yeah , for like two seconds .
Before she dumped him for Steve .
I thought you dumped her for me .
I did . He 's full of shit .
And are the police aware that you dated the victim ?
Hey , what are you saying ? That I killed her ?
It would certainly improve your high school " Q. "
- Stu was with me last night , okay ? - Yeah , I was .
Ooh . Was that before or after he sliced and diced ?
[ Tatum ] Fuck you , nutcase . Where were you last night ?
Working , thank you .
At the video store ? I thought they fired your sorry ass .
Twice .
- I didn 't kill anybody . - Nobody said you did .
Thanks , buddy .
[ Mocking ] Besides , it takes a man to do something like that .
I 'm gonna gut your ass in a second , kid .
Tell me something —
[ Imitating Jerry Lewis ] Did you really put her liver in the mailbox ?
' Cause I heard they found her liver in the mailbox next to her spleen and her pancreas .
Randy , you goon-fuck . I 'm trying to eat here .
She 's getting mad , all right ?
You better liver alone . [ Laughs ]
Liver alone !
[ Laughing ]
Li — Ow ! Liver . Liver . It was a joke .
[ Brakes Squealing ]
- [ Girl # 1 ] See you , Sidney . - [ Girl # 2 ] I 'll talk to you tomorrow , Sid .
So , you sure I can stay over ? ' Cause my dad won 't be back till Sunday .
[ Tatum ] No problem . I 'll pick you up after practice .
You okay ?
Uh-huh . It 's just , you know , the police and reporters and everything .
It 's like déjà vu all over again .
I 'll be there by 7 : 00 . I promise .
- Thanks , Tatum . - Later .
[ Beeps ]
[ Dogs Barking In Distance ]
[ Lock Clicks ]
[ Clock Chiming ]
The bodies of 1 7-year-old Casey Becker and her 18-year-old boyfriend , Steven Orth ,
were discovered late last night by the girl 's parents —
[ Channel Changes ] [ Man ] The Woodsboro double murder case .
Authorities are baffled by the lack of clues and the savage —
The town 's in shock , and no one can quite believe what has happened here ,
although this is not the first time ...
this small community of Woodsboro has endured such tragedy .
Only a year ago , Maureen Prescott , wife and mother ,
was found raped and murdered not far from this peaceful town square .
[ TV Off ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Ticking ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Bird Caws ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Telephone Rings ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Rings ]
[ Beeps ]
Hello ?
Practice ran late . I 'm on my way , okay ?
It 's past 7 : 00 .
Don 't worry . Casey and Steve didn 't bite it till way after 10 : 00 .
Oh . Oh , that 's comforting .
I 'm gonna swing by the video store .
I was thinkin ' Tom Cruise in All The Right Moves .
You know , if you pause it just right , you can see his penis .
Whatever . Just hurry , okay ?
- Ta-ta , Sid . - [ Beeps ]
[ Owl Hoots ]
[ Rings ]
- [ Beeps ] - Tatum , just get in the car —
[ Male Voice ] Hello , Sidney .
Uh — Hi . Who is this ?
You tell me .
Well , I have no idea .
Scary night , isn 't it ?
With the murders and all , it 's like right out of a horror movie or something .
[ Laughs ] Randy , you gave yourself away .
Are you calling from work , ' cause Tatum 's on her way over .
Do you like scary movies , Sidney ?
I like that thing you 're doing with your voice , Randy . It 's sexy .
What 's your favorite scary movie ?
Oh , come on . You know I don 't watch that shit .
Why not ? Too scared ?
No . No . It 's just , what 's the point ? They 're all the same .
Some stupid killer stalking some big-breasted girl who can 't act ,
who 's always running up the stairs when she should be going out the front door .
It 's insulting .
Are you alone in the house ?
[ Sighs ] Randy , that 's so unoriginal . I 'm disappointed in you .
Maybe that 's because I 'm not Randy .
So who are you ?
The question isn 't " Who am I ? " The question is " Where am I ? "
[ Stammering ] So , where are you ?
Your front porch .
Why would you be calling from my front porch ?
That 's the original part .
Oh , yeah ?
Well , I call your bluff .
[ Bird Chirping ]
[ Owl Hooting ]
- So where are you ? - Right here .
[ Wind Chimes Tinkling ]
[ Exhales ]
- Can you see me right now ? - Uh-huh .
Uh-huh . Okay .
What am I doin ' ? Huh ?
Huh ? What am I doin ' ? Hello !
[ Chuckles ] Nice try , Randy .
Tell Tatum to hurry up , okay ? Bye now .
If you hang up on me , you 'll die just like your mother !
Do you wanna die , Sidney ? Your mother sure didn 't .
Fuck you , you cretin !
[ Screams , Grunts ]
No !
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting , Gasping ]
[ Doorknob Rattling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Door Clattering ]
[ Busy Signal ]
Shit !
[ Shivering ]
[ Gasps ] Billy ! God !
Door 's locked . I heard screaming . You all right ?
The killer 's here . He 's in the house .
He 's in the house . He 's gonna kill me . He 's gonna kill me .
He 's gone . He 's gone .
It 's all right .
[ Sobbing , Stops ]
What ?
Sid , what ?
Whoa , whoa , whoa . Wait , wait , Sidney , wait !
Wait , wait , wait , wait ! What 's going on ?
Sidney , come back ! Sidney !
[ Screams ]
Sorry ! I found this .
Come on !
[ Man ] All right . Hold your hands together .
[ Dewey ] Do you wish to give up your right to remain silent ?
[ Handcuffs Clicking ]
I didn 't do anything . [ Siren Wailing ]
Do you wish to give up your right to speak to an attorney ...
and have them present during questioning ?
Ask her . She 'll tell you . Ask her .
- [ Burke ] What do you got , Dewey ? - I caught him , Sheriff .
- Wait ! - Who is that ?
- Billy Loomis . - Sheriff .
Sheriff , call these guys off . I didn 't do it .
[ Groans ] Sheriff , wait . Wait , listen .
Call my dad . Please , call him .
He 'll tell you . Just call him .
Sidney ! Sidney ! [ Engine Starts ]
- How 's she doing ? - Sid 's tougher than she looks .
[ Siren Wailing ] Have to be , all the shit she 's been through .
[ Billy Screaming ] Sid !
Well , we 're seein ' a lot of you today .
You gonna be able to come down to the station and answer a few questions , Sid ?
Oh , shit . Sidney !
God , Sid . I 'm so sorry I was late . Are you all right ?
Tatum , you can 't be here . This is an official crime scene .
- It 's okay . - [ Sighs ]
Her dad 's out of town , all right ? She 's staying with us tonight .
- Does Mom know ? - Yes , doofus .
- Let 's get you out of here . - [ Woman ] She 'll be okay .
- Thanks . - Come on , Sid .
You won 't believe this .
- [ Man ] Right there . - Creepy , huh ?
- [ Man ] Break this up . - I 'll be damned .
- What ? - Jesus ! The camera , hurry !
My name isn 't Jesus .
Sidney , is that you in there ?
Excuse me . Is that Sidney Prescott they took away ?
- I 'm not talking to you . - What happened to her ?
None of your damn business .
I heard something about a costume . Is that true ?
Can you tell me anything ?
Yeah , you 're a real pain in the ass . Leave Sid alone .
Where 's she goin ' ?
- Look . Kenny ? - Yeah ?
I know that you 're about 50 pounds overweight ,
but when I say " hurry , "
please interpret that as " move your fat , tub-of-lard ass now ! "
[ Snorts ]
Did you find him ?
You sure it was the Hilton ?
At the airport .
[ Typing ]
He 's not registered there . [ Sighs ]
Could he have stayed somewhere else ?
I don 't know . I guess . [ Sniffles ]
Don 't worry , Sid . We 'll find him .
[ Man ] Dewey , they got that mask in .
I 'll be right back .
[ Handcuffs Rattling ]
Let me ask you this .
What are you doing with a cellular telephone , son ?
Everybody 's got one , Sheriff .
I didn 't make those calls , I swear .
Why don 't you check the phone bill , for Christ 's sake ?
Call Vital Phone Comp . They got the records of every number dialed .
Thanks , Hank . We 're on top of it .
What were you doing over at Sidney 's house tonight ?
I wanted to see her . That 's all .
And last night ? Sidney said you crawled through her window last night too .
You went out last night ?
[ Stammers ]
I was watching TV . I got bored . I decided to go for a ride .
Did you happen to ride by Casey Becker 's house ?
No . No , I didn 't .
Sheriff , I didn 't kill anybody ,
We 're gonna have to hold you , son , till we get those phone records .
This is crazy .
You know that ? I didn 't do it .
[ Chattering ]
[ Woman ] Camera Two ? Okay .
Are there any more doughnuts in there ?
- Move it , Kenny . - They 're not lettin ' anybody in .
I 'm not just anyone .
[ Mutters ] More like a bitch goddess .
- Kenny , are we on ? - Yeah , go .
Hi . Gale Weathers reporting live from the Woodsboro police station ,
where we hope to get a glimpse of Sidney Prescott .
[ Man ] Hey . Watch it , lady .
Hey , watch the hand ! You know who you 're dealing with here ?
Tell ' em . Come on , Dad . Tell ' em !
- Just wait for the lawyer , Billy . - Sidney !
- Sidney , come on . You know me . - [ Deputy ] Come on , come on .
- Sidney , look at me ! - [ Deputy ] Don 't give us any trouble .
[ Billy ] Come on !
Sid .
We 're gonna get you out of here , okay ? You okay ?
[ Sighs ] They sell this costume at every five-and-dime in the state .
There 's no way to track the purchase .
What about that cellular phone bill ?
We 're pulling Loomis 's account . We won 't know anything until the morning .
[ Tatum ] Oh , come on !
You think he did it ?
Twenty years ago , I would 've said , " Not a chance . "
But these kids today —
[ Snorts ] Damned if I know .
- Hey , Dewey , can we go now ? - Hold on a second .
- Goddamn it , Dewey ! - [ Deputies Mocking ]
What did Mama tell you ? When I wear this badge , you treat me like a man of the law .
I 'm sorry , Deputy Dewey-boy , but we 're ready to go . Now , okay ?
- [ Man ] Whoa . - [ Laughter ]
Take ' em out the back way . Avoid that circus out there .
- Come on . - Don 't touch me !
- He 's my superior ! - Janitors are your superior .
Let 's get back to work !
Isn 't there a back way out of this building ?
Yeah . Down that alley , I think .
You guys stay here . I 'm gonna get the car .
Don 't move . Don 't make a sound .
[ Gale ] There she is . Sidney !
Hi . Some night . What happened ? Are you all right ?
She 's not answering any questions , all right ? Just leave us alone .
No . No , Tatum , it 's okay . She 's just doin ' her job , right , Gale ?
- Yes , that 's right . - So , how 's the book ?
Well , it 'll be out later this year .
Oh . I 'll look for it .
I 'll send you a copy .
[ Grunts ]
[ Kenny ] Ooh ! Jeez .
- [ Kenny ] Nice shot . - [ Gale ] Bitch .
- No , I mean , camera shot . - Where 'd you learn to punch like that ?
God , I loved it . " I 'll send you a copy . "
Bam ! Bitch went down .
" I 'll send you a copy . " Bam ! Sid , superbitch !
You are so cool .
Thought you might want some ice for that right hook .
Thanks .
I 'll be right next door . Try to get some sleep .
Yeah , yeah .
Do you really think Billy did it ? [ Telephone Rings ]
He was there , Tatum .
He was destined to have a flaw . I knew he was too perfect .
[ Knocking ]
- Telephone , honey . - Who is it ?
- It 's for Sid . - My dad ?
- I don 't think so . - [ Tatum ] Take a message .
No . I 'll get it .
How 's she doin ' ?
Hello ?
[ Male Voice ] Hello , Sidney .
No !
Poor Billy boyfriend .
An innocent guy doesn 't stand a chance with you .
Leave me alone !
Looks like you fingered the wrong guy ... again !
[ Knocking ] Who are you ?
- Dewey ! - Hang up , Sid .
Don 't worry . You 'll find out soon enough .
- I promise . - [ Mother ] Dewey !
[ Dial Tone ]
[ Dewey ] What ?
- [ Tatum ] " What ? " - What ?
Hello ?
[ Man ] Sidney Prescott , who escaped a vicious attack last night ,
is the daughter of Maureen Prescott , who was brutally killed last year ...
when convicted murderer Cotton Weary broke into their home ...
and savagely raped and tortured the deceased .
Cotton Weary is currently awaiting appeal for the death sentence handed down ...
after the young Sidney testified against him .
She was the key witness in the state 's case against the —
It 's never gonna stop , is it ?
Billy was released .
His cellular bill was clean . He didn 't make those calls .
We 're checkin ' every cellular account in the county .
Any calls made to you or Casey Becker are being cross-referenced .
It 's gonna take some time , but we 'll find him .
You okay ?
[ Siren Wails ]
Don 't worry , Sid . It 's school . You 'll be safe here .
So how does it feel to be almost brutally butchered ?
Hey , now leave her alone .
People want to know ! They have a right to know !
- [ Dewey ] Leave her alone . - How does it feel ?
[ Dewey ] She just wants to get an education . Turn that thing off .
What ?
[ Mouthing Words ] Just a sec .
Stop right there .
I 'm not here to fight . I just need to talk .
Kenny , camera , now !
- Off the record . No cameras . - Forget it .
Please ? You owe me .
- I owe you shit . - You owe my mother !
Your mother 's murder was last year 's hottest court case .
Somebody was gonna write a book about it .
Right , and it had to be you with all your lies and bullshit theories .
What is your problem ? You got what you wanted .
Cotton Weary 's in jail . They 're gonna gas him .
A book is not gonna change that .
Do you still think he 's innocent ?
Your testimony put him away . It doesn 't really matter what I think .
During the trial , you did all those stories about me . You called me a liar .
I think you falsely identified him , yes .
- Have you talked to Cotton ? - Many times .
And has his story changed ?
Not one word .
He admits to having sex with your mother , but that 's all .
He 's lying . She never would have touched him .
He raped her , and then ... he butchered her .
Her blood was all over his coat .
He was drunk that night .
He left his coat at your house after your mother seduced him .
I saw him leave wearing it .
[ School Bell Rings ] No , you saw someone leave wearing that coat .
The same someone who planted it in Cotton 's car , framing him .
No . Cotton murdered my mother .
You 're not so sure anymore , are you ?
Nice welt , sweetie .
Let 's go , Sid .
- The killer 's still on the loose , isn 't he ? - Come on , Sid .
Those murders are related .
- I 'm sorry I mangled your face . - Wait . Sidney , don 't go !
Just stop , all right ?
[ Students Chattering ]
Jesus Christ !
An innocent man on death row , a killer still on the loose .
Kenny , tell me I 'm dreaming .
- You wanna go live ? - No , no . Not so fast .
We don 't have anything concrete .
This is huge . You can 't just sit on it .
I know ! That 's why we need proof .
If I 'm right about this , I could save a man 's life .
Do you know what that could do for my book sales ?
This is a mistake . I shouldn 't be here .
I want you to meet me right here after class , okay , Sid ?
All right .
Hey , hey .
I haven 't seen Billy around . Is he really pissed ?
You mean after you branded him the Candyman ? No , his heart 's broken .
- Ow ! - Stu !
[ Shrieking ]
[ Gasps ] [ School Bell Rings ]
[ Shrieking Continues ]
Why are they doing this ?
Are you kidding me ? Look at this place . It 's like Christmas .
- Stupidity leak . - Ow . Easy .
Sidney !
- Oh ! Ow ! - Jesus ! Shit !
It 's just me .
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa . You still think it 's me .
No . No , I-I don 't . It 's just —
Somebody was there .
- Billy , someone tried to kill me . - I know , I know .
The cops said I scared him away .
It wasn 't me , Sid .
I know . He called me again last night at Tatum 's house .
You see ? Couldn 't have been me .
I was in jail . Remember ?
I 'm so ... sorry . Please understand .
Understand what ? That I have a girlfriend ...
who would rather accuse me of being a psychopathic killer than touch me ?
- You know that 's not true . - Then what is it ?
What ... is it ?
Billy , I was attacked and nearly filleted last night !
I mean between us .
You haven 't been the same since —
since your mother died .
Is your brain leaking ? My mom was killed . I can 't believe you 're bringing this up !
- I know . It 's been a year . - Tomorrow ! One year tomorrow .
I know . I think it 's time you got over that .
I mean , when my mom left my dad , I accepted it . It 's the way it is .
She 's not comin ' back .
Your parents split up . This is not the same thing .
Your mom left town . She 's not lying in a coffin somewhere .
Okay , okay , okay . I 'm sorry .
It 's a bad analogy .
But it 's just that ...
I want my girlfriend back .
- Sid ! - Billy .
I am sorry if my traumatized life ...
is an inconvenience to you and your perfect existence .
What ? What — Nobody said that . Sid !
Stupid !
You make me so sick !
Your entire havoc-inducing , thieving , whoring generation disgusts me !
So , two of your fellow students just savagely murdered ,
and this is the way you show your compassion and sensitivity , huh ?
Let me tell you something .
You 're both expelled ! Get out !
Come on , Mr. Himbry !
- It was just a joke ! - That 's not fair !
You 're absolutely right . It is not fair .
Fairness would be to rip your insides out , hang you from a tree ...
so we can expose you for the heartless , desensitized little shits that you are .
[ Sighs ]
[ Girl # 1 ] She was never attacked . I think she made it all up .
- [ Girl # 2 ] Why would she lie about it ? - For attention !
The girl has some serious issues .
[ Toilet Flushes ]
And what if she did it ?
What if Sidney killed Casey and Steve ?
[ Girl # 2 ] And why would she do that ?
[ Girl # 1 ] Maybe she had the hots for Steve and killed them both in a jealous rage .
What would Sidney want with Steve ? She has her own bubble-butt boyfriend , Billy .
Maybe she 's a slut , just like her mother .
You 're evil .
Please. it 's a common fact . Her mother was a tramp .
Cut some slack . She watched her mom get butchered .
And it fucked her up royally . Think about it .
Her mother 's death leaves her disturbed and hostile in a cruel and inhumane world .
She 's delusional . " Where 's God ? " Et cetera . Completely suicidal .
One day she snaps . She wants to kill herself ,
but she realizes that teen suicide is out this year ...
and homicide is a much healthier therapeutic expression .
- Where do you get this shit ? - Ricki Lake .
[ Scoffs ] You are pathetic !
[ Door Opens , Closes ]
Pathetic .
[ Hissing ]
[ Male Voice Whispers ] Sidney .
Is someone there ?
[ Door Closes ]
[ Mouths Word ]
[ Shouts ]
[ Shrieking ]
- [ Gasps , Panting ] - [ Woman ] In what appears to be a prank ,
several students were seen wearing scary masks .
School officials have yet to comment ,
but this is known to be the same costume worn by the killer .
Seventeen-year-old Casey Becker and her boyfriend ,
Steven Orth , have already lost their lives .
Who 's next ? You can literally feel the fear on this campus .
Hi ! Gale Weathers , field correspondent , Top Story .
I know who you are , Miss Weathers . How 's the eye ?
It 's productive . Is there a problem on campus ?
No , everything 's under control .
Well , of course . You 're here .
You 're not supposed to be here .
I know . I should be in New York covering the Sharon Stone stalker , but who knew ?
You look awfully young to be a police officer .
I 'm 25 years old .
You know , in a demographic study ,
I proved to be most popular amongst males 1 1 to 24 .
Guess I just missed you . [ Chuckles ]
Course , you don 't look a day over 1 2 .
Except in that upper torso area .
Does the force require you to work out ?
No , ma 'am .
' Cause of my boyish good looks ,
muscle mass has increased my acceptance as a serious police officer .
- [ P. A. : Feedback ] - [ Himbry ] I need your attention now , kids .
Due to the recent events that have occurred ,
effective immediately , all classes are suspended until further notice .
[ Teens Cheering ] The Woodsboro police department has issued a citywide curfew ...
beginning at 9 : 00 tonight . [ Teens Groaning ]
Looks like we 've got a serial killer on our hands .
Serial killer 's not really accurate .
Gotta knock off a couple more to get that title .
Well , we can hope , can 't we ? [ Chuckles ]
I mean , we certainly don 't have any leads .
Have you located Sidney 's father yet ?
No , not yet .
He 's not a suspect , is he ?
We haven 't ruled him out as a ... possibility .
If you 'll excuse me .
I 'm sorry . Am I keeping you ?
If I may say so , Miss Weathers ,
you are much prettier in person .
So you do watch the show .
I 'm 25 . I was 24 for a whole year .
Please , call me Gale .
It was just some sick fuck having a laugh , Sidney .
No . It was him , Tatum . I know it .
Well , you 're not to be alone anymore , right ? If you pee , I pee . Is that clear ?
Cizzool cuz scizzool is izzout .
I don 't know what you did , Sidney , But on behalf of the entire student body ,
- we all say , " Thank you ! " - Drop it , Stu .
I say , impromptu party tonight , my house .
Celebrate this little siesta . What do you say ?
[ Sidney ] Are you serious ?
This little vixen doesn 't invite the entire world , we 'll be fine .
Intimate gathering , intimate friends .
What do you say , Sid ? I mean , pathos could have its perks .
Totally protect you . Yo , I am so buff .
- I got you covered , girl . - I don 't know .
I mean , come on , Sid . For me ? It could be fun .
Okay . Whatever .
Yeah ? Nice .
Cool . You guys bring food , all right ?
[ Imitating Engine ]
[ Growls ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Knocking ]
Yes ?
Hello ?
[ Knocking ]
Damn it .
Damn little shits .
What 'd you call me ? Huh ?
- Not you , Fred . - [ Mutters ] You little prick .
[ Screaming ]
[ Groans ]
[ Man Singing Rock ] ♪ School 's out for summer ♪
♪ School 's out with fever ♪ What if Cotton Weary is telling the truth ?
Maybe he was having an affair with your mom .
I mean , your dad was always out of town on business . Maybe —
Maybe your mom was just a very unhappy woman .
If they were having an affair , how come Cotton couldn 't prove it in court ?
Well , you can 't prove a rumor . That 's why it 's a rumor .
Right . Created by that little tabloid twit , Gale Weathers .
It goes further back , Sid .
[ Exhales ] There 's been talk about other men .
And you believe it .
Well —
I mean , you can only hear that Richard Gere gerbil story so many times ...
before you have to start believing it .
Oh , I 'm sorry .
You know , if I was wrong about Cotton Weary ,
then the killer 's still out there .
Don 't go there , Sid .
You 're starting to sound like some Wes Carpenter flick or something .
Don 't freak yourself out , okay ? We 've got a long night ahead of us .
Okay ?
Let 's boogie .
- It 's alive ! - Henry , in the name of God .
In the name of God ! Now I know —
- Watch it , jerk . - I 'm sorry .
[ Mock Scream , Laughs ]
Dork .
Jesus , this place is packed tonight , man .
- We had a run in the mass murder section . - Comin ' to my fiesta ?
- Yeah , I 'm off early . Curfew , you know . - Cool .
What 's that werewolf movie with E.T. 's mom in it ?
- The Howling . Horror . Straight ahead . - Okay , thanks .
- Oh , now that 's in poor taste . - What ?
If you were the only suspect in a senseless bloodbath ,
would you be standing in the horror section ?
What ? It was just a misunderstanding . He didn 't do anything .
You 're such a little lapdog .
He 's got " killer " printed all over his forehead .
[ Mocking ] Okay ! Really ?
Well , why 'd the cops let him go , smart guy ?
Because obviously they don 't watch enough movies .
This is standard horror movie stuff .
Prom Night revisited , man .
Yeah ? Why would he want to kill his own girlfriend ?
There 's always some stupid , bullshit reason to kill your girlfriend .
- Huh ? - That 's the beauty of it all : simplicity .
Besides , if it gets too complicated , you lose your target audience .
Well , what 's his reason ?
Maybe Sidney wouldn 't have sex with him .
[ Laughs ] What , is she savin ' herself for you ?
Maybe . Now that Billy tried to mutilate her , do you think Sid would go out with me ?
No , I don 't at all . No .
You know who I think it is ?
Yo , I think it 's her father .
Why can 't they find her pops , man ?
Because he 's probably dead .
His body will come poppin ' up in the last reel somewhere !
Eyes gouged out , fingers cut off , teeth knocked out !
The police are always off-track with this shit .
If they 'd watch Prom Night , they 'd save time .
There 's a formula to it . A very simple formula ! Everybody 's a suspect !
I 'm telling you , the dad 's a red herring . It 's Billy .
How do we know you 're not the killer ? Huh ?
- Huh ? - Hi , Billy .
Maybe your movie-freaked mind lost its reality button . You ever think of that ?
You 're absolutely right . I 'm the first to admit it .
If this were a scary movie , I 'd be the prime suspect .
- That 's right . - And what would be your motive ?
It 's the millennium .
Motives are incidental .
Millennium . Hmm .
Millennium . I like that .
That 's good . It 's the millennium .
Good kid .
" Millennium . " Good word , my man .
And you 're telling me that 's not a killer .
♪ ♪ [ Rock Ballad ]
♪ You 'll see him in your nightmares ♪
♪ You 'll see him in your dreams ♪
♪ He 'll appear out of nowhere ♪
♪ But he ain 't what he seems ♪
♪ You 'll see him in your head ♪
♪ On the TVscreen ♪
♪ Hey , buddy , I 'm warnin 'you to turn it off ♪
♪ He 's a ghost , he 's a god ♪
♪ He 's a man , he 's a guru ♪
♪ You 're one microscopic cog in his catastrophic plan ♪
♪ Designed and directed by his red right hand ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues ] [ Dewey ] Sure is quiet .
God , look at this place . It 's The Town That Dreaded Sundown .
Yeah , I saw that movie . It 's about a killer in Texas , huh ?
- Mmm . - Hey , Sid , just think .
If they make a movie about you , who 's gonna play you ?
I shudder to think .
I see you as a young Meg Ryan myself .
Thanks , Dewey . With my luck , they 'd cast Tori Spelling .
I 'm just gonna be a few minutes .
You girls don 't go too far .
Is Billy gonna be there tonight ?
He 'd better not be . I told Stu to keep his mouth shut .
I think we can live without the endorphin rush for one night .
Billy 's right , you know . Whenever he touches me , I just can 't relax .
So you have a few intimacy issues as a result of your mother 's untimely death .
That 's no big deal , Sid . You 'll thaw out .
Yeah , but he has been so patient with me — you know , with all the sex stuff .
How many guys would put up with a girlfriend who 's sexually anorexic ?
Billy and his penis don 't deserve you , all right ?
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
- Dewey , where the hell you been ? - I was keepin ' an eye on Sidney , uh —
Thought you quit .
I did . But damn it —
Dewey , Vital Phone just faxed us .
Those calls are listed to Neil Prescott , Sidney 's father .
He made the calls with a cellular phone . It 's been confirmed .
There 's no way his cellular could 've been cloned ?
There 's more . Guess what tomorrow is .
The anniversary of his wife 's death .
We 'll keep the roadblocks and the curfew in effect through the night .
If he 's not picked up by morning , then we 'll do a house-to-house .
Where 's Sidney ?
She 's with my sister . You want me to bring her in ?
Nah . Not just yet .
Let 's find Neil first , make sure he 's our man .
You stay close to Sidney .
Don 't let her out of your sight .
Yes , sir .
♪ ♪ [ Hard Rock ]
♪ Say a prayer for the youth of America ♪
♪ God bless the youth of America ♪
♪ I can 't stand their sight anymore ♪
All right . You girls have fun .
Not too much fun , or I 'll bust you .
- Bye . - Bye , Sid .
♪ You 're obsessed ♪
- Caterer 's here . - [ Shouting , Whooping ]
Oh . That 's mature .
You guys were tardy for the party , so we started without you .
- My man ! - [ Belches ]
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
[ Engine Off ]
Shh .
Well , were we spotted ?
I don 't think so . Now get the camera .
- I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean to scare you . - [ Sighs ] Deputy , that 's okay .
What brings you to these parts ?
Well , you just never know when or where a story will break .
Not much of a story here . Just a bunch of kids cuttin ' it loose .
Then what are you doing here ?
Just keepin ' an eye on things .
I 'm gonna check the party out .
Do you mind if I join you ?
Not at all .
All right . Let me just get my coat .
- All right . - Yeah , I 'm fine .
Oh ! Yeah .
♪ ♪ [ Rock On Stereo ] How many Evil Deads ?
[ Boy ] Yeah !
- How many Hellraisers ? - Hellraiser right here .
The Fog , Terror Train , Prom Night .
How come Jamie Lee Curtis is in all of these movies ?
She 's the ... scream queen .
With a set of lungs like that , she should be .
- Yeah . - Tits . See ?
[ Doorbell Rings ] Oh , I 'll get it .
[ Woman ] ♪ This time , you 'll listen ♪
Hey , Tate , grab another beer , would you ? [ Rings ]
[ Boy ] There 's beer in the garage .
What am I , the beer wench ?
- And she was nominated . - Oh , yeah ?
She was nominated for Terror Train .
You are not gonna believe who 's here ! It 's that chick from Top Story .
- Gale Weathers ? - Here . Yeah .
- [ Shouting , Chattering ] - Shit !
You 're underage , son .
I 'm kiddin ' . Have a good time . Watch your driving .
- [ Tatum ] Dewey ? - Hi .
Dewey ?
- What is she doing here ? - She 's with me .
- I 'm just checkin ' things out . - So you did .
Now leave , and take your media muff with you .
- I just think you 're awesome . - Oh , thank you very much .
- I watch your show religiously . - That 's great .
- Hey . - Hey .
- I need a camera . - [ Sighs ]
- Did they find my father ? - I 'm afraid not .
- [ Sidney ] Should I be worried ? - [ Dewey ] Not yet .
♪ Get out , you 're walkin ' ♪ [ Boy ] That 's the one I want — Halloween .
♪ Too bad , I 've spoken ♪ [ Chattering Continues ]
♪ When I look at you ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues , Faint ]
[ Muttering ]
♪ You 're forgiven ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues , Faint ]
[ Hinges Squeak ]
- [ Loud Clattering ] - Jesus !
[ Yowls ]
[ Sighs ] Tatum , it 's okay .
Shit .
Hey , shitheads !
Hello !
Shit . Piss .
Is that you , Randy ?
[ Scoffs ] Cute .
And what movie is this from ? I Spit On Your Garage ?
Lose the outfit . If Sidney sees it , she 'll flip .
Oh , you wanna play psycho killer ?
Can I be the helpless victim ?
Okay , let 's see —
No , please don 't kill me , Mr. Ghost Face .
I wanna be in the sequel ! [ Chuckles ]
Cut , Casper . That 's a wrap .
Randy , what the hell are you doing ?
[ Yelps , Grunts ]
[ Screams ] Stop !
[ Groans ]
Fucker !
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunts , Groans ]
[ Grunting , Gasping ]
[ Fabric Tears ]
[ Gasping , Whimpering ]
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming Continues ] No !
[ Splatters ]
[ Hinges Creak ] ♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
- Happy curfew . - [ Girl ] Nice party , Stu .
- Tatum , come on ! - [ Girl ] Nobody here but us chickens !
- Do you know where she is ? - No , I haven 't seen her .
[ Shouts ]
Oh , Billy . Hey .
♪ ♪ [ Blues Rock On Stereo ] Billy . Hmm . What are you doin ' here ?
I was hoping I could talk to Sid alone .
You know , if Tatum sees you here , she 'll draw blood .
I 'll tell you what . Why don 't you guys go up to my parents ' room ?
You know , you guys can talk ,
whatever .
Subtlety , Stu . You should look it up .
No , it 's okay . We do need to talk .
Ooh ! Ow .
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
What 's Leatherface doin ' here ?
Cute . He came to make up .
There goes my chance with Sid . Damn it !
As if .
That 's all I 'm sayin ' . As if .
Oh , really , Alicia ?
" As if . "
I 'm gonna go check on them .
[ Kenny ] Come on !
[ Gale ] Okay , everyone . It was nice to meet all of you .
- Thank you . - Stick around .
[ Laughs ] You 're a genius .
- Oh , shit . - What ?
- I got a delay . - [ Gale ] How long is it ?
I don 't know . What 'd it take you to walk from the house , 30 seconds ?
- It 'll be fine . Just record it . - All right .
Oh , the placement is perfect .
- Tell me , Kenneth — - Hmm ?
Has a cheesy tabloid journalist ever won the Pulitzer ?
Well , first time for everything .
You 're damn right .
So , um —
- [ Sighs ] - So —
I 'm sorry .
I 've been selfish , and I want to apologize .
No , Billy , I 'm ...
the one who 's been selfish and self-absorbed ...
with all this post-traumatic stress .
- You lost your mom . - Yeah , I know , but you 're right .
Enough is enough .
I can 't wallow in the grief process forever , and —
and I can 't ...
keep lying to myself about who my mom was .
[ Sniffles , Sighs ]
Yeah , I think I 'm really ...
scared ...
that I 'm gonna turn out just like her , you know ?
Like The Bad Seed or somethin ' .
And I know it doesn 't make sense .
Yeah , it does .
Hmm .
It 's like Jodie Foster in Silence of the Lambs ,
when she keeps having flashbacks of her dead father .
But this is life .
This isn 't a movie .
Sure it is , Sid .
It 's all — It 's all a movie .
It 's all ...
one great big movie .
Only you can 't pick your genre .
Why can 't I be a Meg Ryan movie ?
Or even a good porno .
What ?
You heard me .
Are you sure ?
Yeah .
I think so .
[ Boy ] Look , look , look . Here it comes .
- Blam ! - Ohh !
The blood is all wrong ! Why do they do that ? It 's too red !
Wait . Here comes another .
[ Muttering ]
- Ooh ! Ooh ! - Yes ! Yes !
Predictable . I knew he was gonna bite it .
- How can you watch this shit over and over ? - Shh !
When do we see breasts ? I wanna see Jamie Lee 's breasts .
- When do we see Jamie Lee 's breasts ? - Breasts ?
Not until Trading Places in ' 83 .
Jamie Lee was always the virgin in horror movies .
She never showed her tits till she went legits .
- Could afford a decent pair . - What 'd you say ?
That 's why she always outsmarted the killer in the big chase scene at the end .
Only virgins can do that . Don 't you know the rules ?
- What rules ? - You don 't —
[ TV : Breathing Heavily ]
Jesus Christ . You don 't know the rules ?
Have an aneurysm , why don 't you ?
There are certain rules that one must abide by ...
in order to successfully survive a horror movie .
For instance , number one : You can never have sex .
[ Jeering ]
Big no-no ! Big no-no !
I 'm a dead man .
Sex equals death . Okay ?
Number two : You can never drink or do drugs .
[ Shouting , Whooping ]
No , the sin factor .
It 's a sin . It 's an extension of number one .
And number three : Never , ever , ever , under any circumstances ,
say " I 'll be right back , " ' cause you won 't be back .
- I 'm gettin ' another beer . You want one ? - Yeah , sure .
- I 'll be right back ! - [ Mock Gasping ]
[ Shouting , Whooping ]
You see ? You push the laws and you end up dead .
Okay ? I 'll see you in the kitchen with a knife .
Only virgins can outsmart the killer in the big chase scene at the end .
- Don 't you know the rules ? - What rules ?
You don 't know the rules ?
There are certain rules that one must abide by —
[ Groans ] Boring .
[ Banging ]
The sheriff just radioed .
Somebody reported a car in the bushes down the road . I 'm gonna go check it out .
- Would you care to join me ? - I 'd love to .
If you 're sure it 's all right .
Uh , ma 'am , I 'm the deputy of this town .
Be right back .
[ Monitor On ] [ Shouting , Whooping ]
You see ? You push the laws and you end up dead .
- Excuse me , ma 'am . - Mm-hmm ?
I thought maybe we 'd walk .
It 's such a nice night out . I got a flashlight .
You 're not scared , are you ?
No .
- All right . - Great .
- Do you know what that constellation is ? - No . What is it ?
- I don 't know . That 's why I was askin ' you . - [ Both Laugh ]
[ Chattering ]
- So what happened to Tatum , Stu ? - She probably got pissed at me and bailed .
- [ Boy ] Bye . - [ Girl ] Bye .
[ Stu Kisses , Moans ]
No , I 'm just kidding . I 'm just kidding .
Hey .
Look ! Here comes the obligatory tit shot !
- Yes ! Oh ! - Lovely !
Beautiful ! Oh ! Oh .
- Oh , my God . - I 'll leave you guys alone .
You are so ...
amazing .
[ Ringing ]
Hello ? Yeah ?
Holy shit .
No — Ho —
Listen up .
They found Principal Himbry dead .
He was gutted and hung from the goalpost on the football field .
So what are we waiting for ?
Let 's go over there before they pry him down !
- [ Whoops ] - Hey .
- [ Boy ] To arms ! To arms ! - Hey .
- Where you guys — - Where did he say he was ?
- At the football field ! - Come on !
Where you guys goin ' ?
We were just gettin ' to the good part .
Hello ? Yeah ?
[ Shouting , Whooping ]
Where you guys —
Whoo ! [ Engine Starts ]
- Whoo ! - ♪ ♪ [ All Singing " Ride of the Valkyries " ]
Hi-ho , Silver ! Let 's go !
[ Owl Hooting ] So , is Dewey your real name ?
No , it 's Dwight .
Dwight ?
- I 'm sorry . - No , that 's all right .
Dewey 's just somethin ' I got stuck with a long time ago .
Well , I like it .
It 's sexy .
- Sexy ? - Mm-hmm .
Ah , it 's just this town 's way of not takin ' me serious .
What about Gale Weathers ? [ Giggles ]
Sounds like I 'm a meteorologist or something .
People treat me like I 'm the Antichrist of television journalism .
I don 't think you 're that bad .
- No ? - No .
[ Shouting , Hooting ]
I think that 's just ' cause you kinda like me .
They sure are comin ' fast . Slow down !
- Freeze ! Jump ! - [ Gale Screams ]
[ Groans ]
I 'm sorry . Are you okay ?
Yeah .
I 'm sorry . I 'm on duty .
[ Chuckling ]
Is that what you 're looking for ?
My whole life .
- Damn ! - What ?
- What is it ? - This is Neil Prescott 's car .
- Sidney 's father ? - Yeah .
Jesus . What 's he doing here ?
We gotta get back .
You okay ?
Yeah .
Yeah , I 'm fine . [ Chuckles ]
Who 'd you call ?
What ?
Well , I don 't know —
When you 're arrested , you 're allowed one phone call ,
so I was just curious — who 'd you call ?
Called my dad .
No , um , Sheriff Burke called your dad . I saw him .
Yeah , but when I called I didn 't get an answer .
Huh .
You don 't still think it was me , do you ?
[ Chuckles ] No .
No . I was just thinking if it were you ,
it 'd be a very clever way to throw me off track .
You know , using your one phone call to call me so I wouldn 't think it was you .
That 's all .
Really ?
What do I have to do to prove to you that I 'm not a killer ?
- Oh , my God . - Huh ?
Oh , my God .
- Sidney — - Billy , watch out !
- [ Grunts ] - [ Screams ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Wheezing ] Sid .
[ Pounding ]
[ Groans ]
- [ Pounding ] - Shit !
Help me , somebody ! Help me !
[ Gasping , Panting ]
[ Yelps , Gasps ]
Help me !
[ Screaming ]
[ Screams ]
[ Retches ]
No , Jamie . Uh , watch out .
Watch out , Jamie . You know he 's around .
You — You know —
Look , there he is . I told you .
I told you he was right around the corner .
Jamie . Jamie .
Jamie , look behind you . Look behind you .
Turn around . Behind you .
Oh , turn — Behind you !
Behind , Jamie .
Jamie , turn around .
Oh , God ! Yeah .
Help me ! Help ! [ Panting ]
- [ Pounding ] - Let me in !
The killer 's coming after me ! He 's in the house !
Where ? Wait , wait .
- There 's a camera in the house . Look . - Behind you !
- Oh , God . No . - Oh , shit .
Jamie . Jamie .
- Behind you , kid ! - Randy !
- Behind you ! - Look around !
- Shit . - What ?
- We 're on 30-second delay . - Oh , my God .
[ Screams ]
[ Gasping , Whimpering ]
The ... door .
[ Kenny Groans ] [ Body Thuds ]
[ Screams ]
- Is there a phone in the van ? - Yeah .
Lock yourself in it . Call the sheriff for backup .
Be careful !
[ - Grunts ] - [ Woman Screaming On TV ]
- [ Grunts ] - [ Whimpering ]
- Neil ? - [ Whimpering Continues ]
[ Weeping ]
Mr. Prescott ?
Shit !
[ Screams ]
Oh ! [ Groaning ]
[ Clears Throat ]
Kenny , I need the cellular !
Kenny !
[ Echoing ]
[ Squishes ]
[ Beeping , Line Rings ]
- [ Woman ] 9-1-1 . - What 's going on ?
- [ Screaming ] - [ Grunting , Groans ]
- [ Body Thuds ] - [ Engine Starts ]
Oh , God !
[ Whimpering ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Screams ]
Oh ! [ Gasping ]
Oh , God . Kenny , I 'm sorry , but get off my fucking windshield !
Stop !
- [ Screams ] - [ Tires Screeching ]
Oh , God !
[ Crying ]
[ Panting ] Dewey !
[ Echoing ]
Dewey , where are you ? [ Echoing ]
Dewey !
Sidney ?
Shit !
[ Tapping ]
[ Jingling ]
[ Woman On Police Radio ] 7825 , suspect at 105 North Avenue 52 .
Hello . Help me , please . I 'm at Stu Marker 's house on Turner Lane .
It 's 261 Turner Lane .
Please . He 's gonna try and kill me .
- [ Yells ] - [ Grunting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Randy ] Sidney !
Sidney ! Jesus , we 've gotta get the fuck out of here !
Stop right there !
Don 't shoot . It 's me ! I found Tatum . She 's dead !
- I think Stu did it . - Don 't listen to him , Sidney !
- Stay back ! - Stu did it .
- He killed Billy . He killed my Tatum . - You did it !
- He killed my Tatum ! - No , I didn 't !
You lie ! Sidney , baby . Please , give me that gun !
Give me that gun ! Christ , man !
No , I didn 't . No , I didn 't ! Sid , he did it ! He did it , Sidney !
Please , I didn 't do it . He did it . Please !
- Please , Sidney . Oh ! - Fuck you both !
- Please ! - No ! No ! Sidney !
- [ Banging ] - Open up !
[ Grunts ] Help me ! He 's going crazy !
- Sidney ! - Go away !
- [ Banging ] - Sidney ?
[ Whispers ] Leave me alone .
[ Grunting ]
- Sid . - Billy .
[ Groans ]
Oh ! Billy . Billy . Are you okay ?
- I 'm okay . - I thought you were dead .
No . Bleeding like a stuck pig , but I 'm all right .
Get up .
- I 'm okay . - You 're bleeding .
- Oh , my God . - We 've gotta get help .
No , he 's out there !
No , give me the gun . Give me the gun . It 's okay .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
Careful .
- Please help me ! - Whoa , whoa . Come here , come here !
Stu 's flipped out ! He 's gone mad !
We all go a little mad sometimes .
- No , Billy ! - Oh , fuck !
[ Screams ]
- [ Moans ] - [ Sobs ]
Anthony Perkins , Psycho .
[ Panting ]
Mmm .
Corn syrup . Same stuff they used for pig 's blood in Carrie .
No .
[ Gasps ] Stu .
Help me , please .
[ Male Voice ] Surprise , Sidney .
- No ! - [ Stu ] Ooh !
Oh , now . Whoa .
[ Male Voice ] What 's the matter , Sidney ? You look like you 've seen a ghost .
[ Gasps ] Why are you doing this ?
It 's all part of the game , Sidney .
- It 's called " Guess How I 'm Gonna Die . " - Fuck you !
No , no , no , no , no .
We already played that game , remember ?
- You lost . - It 's a fun game , Sidney .
See , we ask you a question , and if you get it wrong ,
bookah — you die !
You get it right , you die .
You 're crazy , both of you .
Actually , we prefer the term " psychotic . "
You 'll never get away with this .
Oh , no ?
Tell that to Cotton Weary .
You wouldn 't believe how easy he was to frame .
Watch a few movies , take a few notes .
- It was fun . - No !
- Whoa ! - Where you goin ' ?
[ Sobbing ] Why ?
- [ Slaps Counter ] - Why did you kill my mother ?
Why ? [ Shouts ] Why ?
You hear that , Stu ? I think she wants a motive .
[ Chuckling ]
I don 't really believe in motive , Sid .
I mean , did Norman Bates have a motive ?
No .
Did they ever really decide why Hannibal Lecter liked to eat people ? Don 't think so !
See , it 's a lot scarier when there 's no motive , Sid .
We did your mom a favor , Sid . That woman was a slut-bag whore ...
who flashed her shit all over town like she was Sharon Stone .
[ Stu ] Yeah , we put her out of her misery , ' cause let 's face it , Sidney ,
your mother was no Sharon Stone , huh ?
Is that motive enough for you ?
Well , how ' bout this ?
Your slut mother was fucking my father ,
and she 's the reason my mom moved out and abandoned me .
How 's that for a motive ?
Maternal abandonment causes serious deviant behavior .
Certainly fucked you up . It made you have sex with a psychopath .
That 's right . You gave it up .
Now you 're no longer a virgin .
[ Giggles ] I said " virgin . " Whoops !
Now you gotta die . Those are the rules .
Just pretend it 's all a scary movie , Sid . How do you think it 's gonna end ?
Oh ! Oh ! This is the greatest part ! You 're gonna love this .
We got a surprise for you , Sidney .
Yeah , you 're gonna love this one . It 's a scream , baby !
Hold on a sec . I 'll be right back . [ Mock Scream ]
You know what time it is , Sid ?
It 's after midnight .
It 's your mom 's anniversary . Congratulations .
We killed her exactly one year ago today .
Attention ! Oh !
What do we have behind door number three , Sidney ?
- Daddy ! - Whoa , hold it .
That 's enough .
[ Male Voice ] Guess we won 't be needing this anymore .
And , oh , look at this . Ring , ring . Won 't need this .
Got the ending figured out yet , Sid ?
Come on , Sidney . You think about it now , huh ?
Your daddy 's the chief suspect . We cloned his cellular .
Evidence is all right there , baby !
What if your father snapped ? Your mother 's anniversary set him off ,
and he went on a murder spree , killing everyone .
Except for Billy and me . We were left for dead .
Then he ... kills you ...
and shoots himself in the head .
- Perfect ending . - I thought of that .
Watch this .
- Ready ? - Yeah .
Yeah ! I 'm ready , baby !
Hit it ! Get up ! Yeah , babe , get up ! Hit it !
- [ Groans ] - [ Gasps ]
Good one , man . Jesus .
Oh , shit . My turn .
Don 't forget . Stay to the side and don 't go too deep .
Okay . I 'll remember .
[ Screams ] Fuck ! Fuck !
Fuck ! Goddamn it , Stu !
Sorry , Billy . I guess I got a little too zealous , huh ?
- Give me the knife . - No .
Give me the knife !
Now !
You see , Sid , everybody dies but us . Everybody dies but us .
We get to carry on and plan the sequel ,
' cause let 's face it , baby , these days you gotta have a sequel !
[ Stabbing ] [ Stu Groaning ]
You sick fucks . You 've seen one too many movies .
Now , Sid , don 't you blame the movies .
Movies don 't create psychos . Movies make psychos more creative !
[ Yelps ]
Stop it , Billy , would you ? All right ?
I can 't take anymore . I 'm feeling a little woozy here !
All right . All right , you get the gun .
And I 'll untie Pops , okay ?
[ Dripping ]
- Now ! - Okay .
- [ Dripping Continues ] - [ Exhales ]
Um . Uh —
Houston , we have a problem here .
- What ? - The gun , man . The gun .
I put it right there , and it 's not there .
Where the fuck is it ?
[ Hammer Cocks ] Right here , asshole .
- Excuse me . I thought she was dead . - She looked dead , man . Still does .
I 've got an ending for you .
The reporter left for dead in the news van ...
comes to ,
stumbles on you two dipshits ,
finds the gun ,
foils your plan and saves the day .
I like that ending .
I know something you don 't .
Fuck . No !
[ Grunts ]
Yeah , man .
Yeah . Aw , so sweet .
Works better without the safety on .
[ Neck Bones Crack ]
[ Panting ]
This is Gale Weathers , signing off .
Baby , you 're gonna love this !
Shit .
What ?
Where are they ? Where are they ?
[ Coughs ] I don 't know , but I 'm hurtin ' , man .
[ Phone Ringing ] Fuck !
Should I let the machine get it ? [ Ringing Continues ]
- Hello ? - [ Male Voice ] Are you alone in the house ?
Bitch ! You bitch ! Where the fuck are you ?
Not so fast . We 're gonna play a little game . It 's called —
[ Sidney ] " Guess who just called the police and reported your sorry motherfucking ass . "
Find her , you dipshit ! Get up !
I can 't , Billy . You cut me too deep .
I think I 'm dying here , man .
[ Weeping ]
Talk to her . Talk to her .
Hello ?
Oh , Stu , Stu , Stu .
What 's your motive ? Billy 's got one .
The police are on their way . What are you gonna tell them ?
Peer pressure . I 'm far too sensitive .
I 'm gonna rip you up , you bitch , just like your fucking mother !
You 've gotta find me first , you pansy-assed mama 's boy !
Fuck !
Ow . You fuckin ' hit me with the phone , dick !
Fucker , where are you ?
[ Yelling ] [ Fabric Tearing ]
- You fuck ! [ Roars ] - [ Crashing ]
Did you really call the police ?
You bet your sorry ass I did .
My mom and dad are gonna be so mad at me .
[ Yells ] Bitch !
[ Whimpering ] [ Clattering ]
[ Whimpering , Screaming ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Groans ]
[ Yelps ]
[ Pistol Clatters ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Grunts ] - [ Groans ]
Oh ! My arm !
- [ Yelling ] - [ Grunts ]
I always had a thing for you , Sid !
[ Screams ]
Bitch .
In your dreams .
[ Screams ]
[ Yelping ]
[ Groans ]
- [ Gasps ] - I 'm sorry . It 's all right .
Oh , my God , Randy , I thought you were dead .
I probably should be . I never thought I 'd be so happy to be a virgin .
- [ Gasps ] - Fucker !
[ Grunting ]
- [ Gasps ] - Say hello to your mother .
[ Screaming ]
[ Yelps , Groans ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Randy Groans ]
[ Sidney Gasps ] [ Randy Groaning ]
- Come on . - [ Whimpers ]
It 's okay .
Guess I remembered the safety that time , you bastard .
Careful .
This is the moment when the supposedly dead killer comes back to life ...
for one last scare .
- [ Grunts ] - [ Screams ]
Not in my movie .
[ Crash ] [ Screaming ]
[ Muffled Grunting ]
[ Exhales ] Dad .
Randy , help me out .
- Ah . Ah . - You okay ?
[ Sidney ] I 'm sorry . Sorry , sorry , sorry .
- Are you okay ? - Yeah .
- Hang in there , buddy . - All right .
- Over here . - Sorry , kid .
Okay , I think it 's gonna go something like this . Just stay with me .
[ Siren Wailing ] Hi , this is Gale Weathers ...
with an exclusive eyewitness account of this amazing breaking story .
Several more local teens are dead ,
bringing to an end the harrowing mystery of the mass killing ...
that has terrified this peaceful community like the plot of some scary movie .
It all began with a scream over 9-1-1 ...
and ended in a bloodbath that has rocked the town of Woodsboro ,
all played out here in this peaceful farmhouse ,
far from the crimes and the sirens of the larger cities that its residents had fled .
Okay , let 's take it back to one . Come on , move it .
This is my big shot . Let 's go .
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
♪ ♪ [ Pop ]
[ Woman ] ♪ Love comes down upon us and it flows like water ♪
♪ Burning with the hope of insight ♪
♪ Feathered books , the colors of a bright elation ♪
♪ Stolen in the sight of love ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are , we 're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are rather helpless ♪
♪ Change is forever A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Birds fly in the eye of the faithless daughter ♪
♪ Spoken at the bitter end ♪
♪ Wasted , sacrificed for the new nirvana ♪
♪ Nighttime sends the sun away ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are , we 're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are rather helpless ♪
♪ Change is forever A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are , we 're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are , we are , we are rather helpless ♪
♪ Change is forever A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪ ♪ A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪ ♪ Whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪
♪ ♪ [ Fades ]
♪ ♪ [ Rock ] [ Man ] ♪ Look outside of my window ♪
♪ But all I see is the rain come down ♪
♪ A pink umbrella and a bit of her leg ♪
♪ Is all I need and I 'll come , come ♪
♪ I don 't care if you don 't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don 't be shy and I 'll show you , baby ♪
♪ What 's it like to be free ♪
♪ I don 't care if you don 't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don 't be shy and I 'll show you , baby ♪
♪ What it 's like to be free ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I don 't care if you don 't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don 't be shy and I 'll show you , baby ♪
♪ What it 's like to be free ♪
♪ Don 't be shy ♪ ♪ Told you , baby ♪
♪ Don 't be shy ♪
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]